Guide to the James O. Brown Associates Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Author File
  - Brinkerhoff, Robert W. (Box 42)
  - Brinton, Henry (Box 42)
  - Bristol, Mark Lambert (Box 42)
  - Britton, Frank L. (Box 42)
  - Broat, I.G. (Box 42)
  - Brody, Catharine (Box 42)
  - Bromfield, Louis (Box 42)
  - Bronner, Cleveland (Box 42)
  - Brook, Danaë (Box 42)
  - Brooke, Gladys Milton Palmer, Dayang Muda of Saraw (Box 42)
  - Brooke, Michael Zachary & H. Lee Remmers (Box 42)
  - Brookes, Pamela (Pamela Susannah Guy Jones) (Box 42)
  - Brooks, David H. (Box 42)
  - Brooks, S. Kent (Box 42)
  - Brotherton, Joe (Box 42)
  - Broun, Heywood Campbell (Box 43)
  - Brower, Millicent (Box 43)
  - Brown, A. Roy (Box 43)
  - Brown, Allan R. (Box 43)
  - Brown, Arthur William (Box 43)
  - Brown, Charles Henry (Box 43)
  - Brown, Clark (Box 43)
  - Brown, Harrison (Box 43)
  - Brown, Henry (Box 43)
  - Brown, Irene Bennett (Box 43)
  - Brown, Joanna (Joanna Brodkey) (Box 43)
    ("Jane Erlich")
  - Brown, John (Box 43)
  - Brown, John Andrew (Box 43)
  - Brown, John Lackey (Box 43)
  - Brown, Pamela (Box 43)
  - Brown, Richard H. (Box 44)
  - Brown, Robin & Julian Pettifer (Box 44)
  - Brown, Stuart (Box 44)
  - Brown, Thomas K., III (Box 44)
  - Browne, Corinne (Box 45)
  - Browne, Lewis (Box 45)
  - Browne, Mary K. (Box 45)
  - Browne, Porter Emerson (Box 45)
  - Browne, Robert (Box 45)
    ("A.F. Scott")
  - Brownell, Marie O. (Box 45)
  - Brownell, William (Box 45)
  - Bruce, Carol • (Box 45)
  - Bruce, Muriel (Box 45)
  - Bruce, Sylvia Valerie (Box 45)
  - Brucker, Carl Gerard (Box 45)
  - Bruff, Nancy (Nancy B. Gardner) (Box 45)
  - Brunner, Bernard A. (Box 45)
  - Bruno, Harry A. (Box 45)
  - Brush, Bernice B. (Box 45)
  - Brush, Katharine (Katharine Ingham Brush Winans) (Box 45)
  - Bryan, Dan (Box 46)
  - Bryan, Joseph, III (Box 46)
  - Bryant, Gay (Box 46)
  - Bryant, Harry Edward Cowan (Box 46)
  - Bryer, Morton (Box 46)
  - Buchanan, Betty Joan (Box 46)
    ("Joan Shepherd")
  - Buchanan, Thompson (Box 46)
  - Buck, Frank (Box 47-48)
  - Buckley, Peter (Box 49)
  - Bucky, Frida Sarsen (Box 49)
  - Bullins, Ed (Box 49)
  - Bullock, A. Archibald (Box 49)
  - Bullock, Alan Louis Charles Bullock, Baron & Oliver Stallybrass (Box 49)
  - Burch, Charles (Box 49)
  - Burch, Claire (Box 49)
  - Burchell, Samuel C. (Box 49)
  - Burgess, Gelett (Box 49)
  - Burgess, William Vincent (Box 49)
  - Burke, David (Box 49)
  - Burkhart, Ann (Box 49)
  - Burkholz, Herbert (Box 49)
  - Burman, Ben Lucian (Box 49)
  - Burne, Frances (Box 49)
  - Burns, Elizabeth (Box 49)
  - Burton, Anthony & Anthony Schiano (Box 50)
  - Burton, LaVerne (Box 50)
  - Burton, Percy (Box 50)
  - Burton, Philip (Box 50)
  - Busch, Frederick (Box 51)
  - Busch, Mrs. Noel (Box 51)
  - Bush, Leslie J. (Box 51)
  - Bush, Roger (Box 51)
  - Butcher, Harry C. (Box 51)
  - Butcher, Margaret (Box 51)
  - Buterbaugh, Elsie (Box 51)
  - Butler, Diana (Diana B. Thomson) (Box 51)
  - Butler, Gerald (Box 51)
  - Butler, Josephine (Box 51)
  - Butler, Ragan (Box 51)
  - Butler, Winifred (Wyn Munro) (Box 51)
  - Buzan, Tony (Box 51)
  - Byard, Margaret Mather (Box 52)
  - Byram, George (Box 52)
  - Byrnes, James Francis (Box 52)
  - Byron, Stuart (Box 52)
  - Caddick, Edward (Box 52)
  - Caesar, Irving (Box 52)
  - Cahen, Fritz Max & Wythe Williams (Box 52)
  - Cahill, J.F. (Box 52)
  - Caillaux, Joseph Marie August e & Robert Pelletier (Box 52)
  - Caldwell, B. Palmer, Jr. (Box 52)
  - Caldwell, Erskine (Box 53-65)
  - Calhoun, Daisy Breaux (Box 66)
  - Callenbach, Ernest (Box 66)
  - Callender, G.A. (Deborah M. Robson) (Box 66)
  - Callender, Harold (Box 66)
  - Callow, Philip (Box 66)
  - Calmer, Ned (Box 66)
  - Calvin, Henry (Clifford Hanley) (Box 66)
  - Cambigue, Susan (Box 66)
  - Cameron, Ralph Henry (Box 66)
  - Camilleri, Joseph (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Bernard G. (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Jean Hamilton (Jean Bachmann) (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Margaret (Margaret C. Beare) (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Michael Mussen, 4th Baron Glenavy (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Patrick Gordon, 3rd Baron Glenavy (Box 66)
  - Campbell, Priscilla Townsend (Box 66)
  - Camps, Francis E. & Richard Barber (Box 66)
  - Canaway, William H. (Box 67)
    ("Bill Price-Hamilton")
  - Canning, Victor (Box 67)
  - Cannon, Poppy (Poppy Whitney Cannon Askland Phillipe White) (Box 67)
  - Cantor, Eddie (Box 67)
  - Card, Helen (Box 67)
  - Cardoza, J. Byrd N. (Box 67)
  - Cardozo, Arlene Rossen (Box 68)
  - Cardozo, Nancy (Box 68)
  - Carey, Ernestine Gilbreth (Box 69)
  - Carlée, Randolph Dreux Lothrop (Box 69)
  - Carlée, Roberta Baughman Hatfield "Baughman Cash" (Box 69)
  - Carlisle. Helen Grace (Box 69)
  - Carlson, Evans F. (Box 69)
  - Carnegie, Dale (Box 69)
  - Carnegie, Sacha (Box 69)
  - Carol II, King of Rumania (Box 70)
  - Carper, Joseph B. (Box 70)
  - Carr, Edward Hallett (Box 70)
  - Carr, John Dickson (Box 70)
    ("Carter Dickson", "John Rhode")
  - Carr, Mary (Box 70)
  - Carr, Raymond (Box 70)
  - Carrel, Alexis (Box 70)
  - Carroll, Raymond G. (Box 70)
  - Carroll, Richard A. (Box 70)
  - Carse, Robert (Box 70)
  - Carson, Gerald (Box 70)
  - Carson, Saul (Box 70)
  - Carson, Xanthus (Box 70)
  - Carter, Boake (Box 71)
  - Carter, Jimmy (Box 71)
  - Carter, John Franklin (Box 71)
    ("Jay Franklin")
  - Carton, Jane (Box 71)
  - Carvic, Heron (Box 71)
  - Cary, Joyce (Box 71)
  - Case, Frank (Box 71)
  - Case, William (Box 71)
  - Casey, Richard Gardner (Box 71)
  - Casey, Robert J. (Box 71)
  - Castle, Everett Rhodes (Box 71)
  - Caswell, Don (Box 71)
  - Catalano, Michael (Box 71)
  - Caughman, John E. (Box 71)
  - Cavanaugh, Arthur (Box 71)
  - Cawthorne, Graham (Box 71)
  - Cayce, William G. (Box 71)
  - Cecil, Henry (Henry Cecil Leon) (Box 71)
  - Cecil, James M. (Box 71)
  - Cecil, Patricia (Box 71)
  - Chaffin, Lillie D. (Box 72)
  - Chamberlain, John (Box 72)
  - Chamberlin, Jo Hubbard (Box 72)
  - Chambrun, Clara Eleanor Longworth, Comtesse de (Box 72)
  - Chapman, Arthur (Box 72)
  - Chapman, John (Box 72)
  - Chapman, Maristan (John Stanton Higham Chapman & Mary Hamilton Illsley Chapman) (Box 72)
  - Chappell, Mollie B. (Box 72)
  - Charell, Lissa (Box 72)
  - Charles, Theresa (Box 72)
  - Chase, Allan (Box 72)
  - Chautemps, Camille (Box 72)
  - Chesney, Kellow (Box 72)
  - Chevalier, Haakon (Box 72)
  - Child, Dorothy G. Everson (Box 72)
  - Chiles, Webb (Box 72)
  - Chisholm, Joe (Box 72)
  - Chitty, Susan Elspeth Glossop (Box 73)
  - Choat, B.R. (Box 73)
  - Chou, Eric (Box 73)
  - Christian, Tina Chad (Christine Elaine Chadwick) (Box 73)
  - Christie, Sherry (Box 73)
  - Church, Joseph (Box 73)
  - Churchill, Douglas W. (Box 74)
  - Churchill, Randolph Frederick Edward Spencer & Winston Spencer Churchill (Box 74)
  - Churchill, Sarah Millicent Hermione Spencer (Box 74)
  - Churchill, Sir Winston Leonard Spencer (Box 74)
  - Chute, Arthur Hunt (Box 74)
  - Ciampi, Elgin T. (Box 74)
  - Cicognani, Bruno (Box 74)
  - Ciliberti, Charles (Box 74)
  - Clairmont, Leonard & Ingrid (Box 74)
  - Clapp, Elsie Ripley (Box 74)
  - Clapper, Raymond (Box 74)
  - Clapperton, Richard Guy- (Box 74)
  - Clark, Alan (Box 74)
  - Clark, Bennett Champ (Box 74)
  - Clark, Blake (Box 74)
  - Clark, George Edward (Box 74)
  - Clark, Jere W. (Box 74)
  - Clark, John Richard (Box 74)
  - Clark, Marguerite (Box 74)
  - Clark, Neil McCullough (Box 74)
  - Clarke, James (Box 75)
  - Clarke, John Pepper (Box 75)
  - Clarke, Pauline Hilda (Box 75)
    ("Helen Clare", (Pauline Hunter Blair))
  - Cleary, F.J. (Box 75)
  - Clendening, Logan (Box 75)
  - Cless, George H., Jr. (Box 75)
  - Cleveland, Patience Mather (Box 75)
  - Clewes, Dorothy M. (Box 75)
  - Clewes, Howard Charles Vivian (Box 75)
  - Clift, Glenn G. (Box 75)
  - Clifton, Pat & Charles Burch (Box 75)
  - Cloete, Stuart (Box 75)
  - Coakley, Mary Lewis & Mario A. Castallo (Box 76)
  - Cochran, Louis (Box 76)
  - Cochrane, Edward ¥. (Box 76)
  - Cochrell, Boyd (Box 76)
  - Cockrell, Ewing (Box 76)
  - Coe, Charles Martin (Box 76)
  - Coetzee, John (Box 76)
  - Coffey, Thomas M. (Box 76)
  - Coffin, Howard Macy & W.L* River (Box 76)
  - Coffman, Virginia & Donnie (Box 76)
  - Micciche Coffman (Box 76)
  - Coggeshall, Susanna Wilson (Box 76)
  - Cohn, Alfred A. (Box 76)
  - Conn, Saul (Box 76)
  - Colcord, Lincoln Ross (Box 76)
  - Cole, (Major) (Box 76)
  - Cole, Hubert Archibald Noel (Box 76)
  - Cole, William (Box 76)
  - Coleman, Lonnie (William Laurence Coleman) (Box 77-79)
    (PRTS James O. Brown)
  - Coles, Manning (Cyril Henry Coles & Adelaide Frances Manning) (Box 80)
  - Collidge, Harold C. (Box 80)
  - Collier, James Lincoln (Box 80)
  - Collier, Joy (Box 80)
  - Collier, Richard (Box 80)
  - Collings, Kenneth B. (Box 80)
  - Collins, Carvel (Box 80)
  - Collins, Frederick Lewis (Box 80)
  - Collins, Margaret (Box 80)
  - Collins, Nancy Duvall (Box 80)
  - Colman, Hila C. (Box 81)
  - Colton, Willard A. (Box 81)
  - Colwell, Robert (Box 81)
  - Colwell, Robert T. (Box 81)
  - Compton-Burnett, Ivy (Box 81)
  - Conconi, Charles N. & Toni House (Box 82)
  - Conklin, W.R. (Box 82)
  - Connolly, Vera L. (Box 82)
  - Connors, Thomas E. (Box 82)
  - Conrad, Eugene (Box 82)
  - Considine, John L. (Box 82)
  - Consolo, Bonnie (Box 82)
  - Constable, George (Box 82)
  - Conway, Laura (Box 82)
  - Cook, James Graham (Box 82)
  - Cook, Joe (Box 82)
  - Cook, Kenneth (Box 82)
  - Cook, Margaret (Box 82)
  - Cooke, Phyl (Box 82)
  - Cooke, Ronald U. & John C. Doornkamp (Box 82)
  - Cookson, Peter (Box 82)
  - Cooper, Courtney Ryley (Box 82)
  - Cooper, Douglas E. (Box 82)
  - Cooper, Frank (Box 82)
  - Cooper, Harold Heaton (Box 82)
  - Cooper, Lettice (Box 82)
  - Coppel, Alfred (Box 83)
    ("A.C. Marin")
  - Copperman, Paul (Box 83)
  - Coppotelli, Arthur (Box 83)
  - Corcoran, William W. (Box 83)
  - Cordaiy, Hunter (Box 83)
  - Cordell, Alexander (George Alexander Graber) (Box 83)
  - Corley, Edwin (Box 84)
    ("Patrick Buchanan", "David Harper", "William Judson")
  - Corliss, Allene (Box 84)
  - Cornick, Katharine Tuttle (Box 84)
  - Corral, Francis S. (Box 84)
  - Corrigan, Joseph Eugene (Box 84)
  - Corrigan, Michael (Box 84)
  - Corsi, Edward (Box 84)
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara (Box 84)
  - Costello, William (Box 84)
  - Cotler, Gordon (Box 85)
  - Cott, Ted (Box 85)
  - Cottles, Catherine Emerson (Box 85)
  - Cotzias, Costas G (Box 85)
  - Coughlin, Gene (Box 85)
  - Counihan, Daniel (Box 85)
  - Courtney, Charles (Box 85)
  - Courtney, F.T. (Box 85)
  - Cowell, Adrian (Box 85)
  - Cox, Geoffrey (Box 85)
  - Cox, Richard A. (Box 85)
  - Coxey, Jacob Sechler (Box 85)
  - Coyne, John (Box 85)
  - Craddock, James H. (Box 85)
  - Craig, John (Box 85)
  - Craig, Morris H. (Box 85)
  - Crail, Joe & Charles S. (Box 85)
  - Craven, Thomas (Box 86)
  - Craven, William D. (Box 86)
  - Crawford, Marion (Box 86)
  - Creager, Marvin H. (Box 86)
  - Creech, Jim (James Rufus Creech) & Avri El-Ad (Box 86)
  - Creed, Will (Box 86)
  - Creedy, Richard F. (Box 86)
  - Creel, George (Box 86)
  - Crenshaw, Files, Jr. (Box 86)
  - Cressy-Marcks, Violet Olivia Rutley (Violet Fisher) (Box 86)
  - Crick, Francis harry Compton (Box 87)
  - Crissey, A. Elwell (Box 87)
  - Crissey, Forrest (Box 87)
  - Critelli, Ann D. (Box 87)
  - Crocker, Barbara J. (Box 87)
  - Crockett, Albert Stevens (Box 87)
  - Crockett, Newkirk (Box 87)
  - Cronyn, George William (Box 87)
  - Crosby, E.S. (Box 87)
  - Crosby, Larry & Bing (Box 87)
  - Cross, Beverley (Box 87)
  - Cross, Ethan Allen (Box 87)
  - Crowder, Michael (Box 87)
  - Crowe, Bettina Lum, Lady (Box 87)
    ("Peter Lum")
  - Crowell, James R. (Box 87)
  - Crowell, Joan & David (Box 87)
  - Crowther, John (Box 87)
  - Croy, Homer (Box 87)
  - Cudahy, John (Box 87)
  - Cudahy, Sheila (Box 87)
  - Cunningham, Bill (Box 88)
  - Curley, Ralph (Box 88)
  - Curley, Walter Joseph Patrick, Jr. (Box 88)
  - Curnow, Allen (Box 88)
  - Curran, Charles W. (Box 88)
  - Curtis, James R. (Box 88)
  - Curtsinger, E.C., Jr. (Box 88)
  - Curzon, Daniel (Daniel R. Brown) (Box 88)
  - Czarnowska, Marta (Box 88)
  - Czernin, Ferdinand, Count (Box 88)
  - Dacey, Norman F. (Box 89)
  - Daché, Lilly (Box 89)
  - Dale, Celia (Celia Marjorie Ramsey) (Box 89)
  - Dale, George (Box 89)
  - D'Alpuget, Lou (Box 89)
  - Dalton, David (Box 89)
  - Dalton, Katharina (Box 89)
  - Dane, Clemence (Winifred Ashton) (Box 89)
  - Daneman, Meredith (Box 89)
  - Danenhower, Sloan (Box 89)
  - Daniel, Glyn Edmund (Box 89)
  - Daniell, Francis Raymond (Box 89)
  - Darack, Arthur (Box 89)
  - Darling, Jay Norwood (Box 89)
    ("J.N. Ding")
  - Darlington, William Aubrey (Box 89)
  - Darroch, Colin: (Box 89)
  - Darroch, Harry D. (Box 89)
  - Darrock, Sandra Jobson (Box 89)
  - Dars, Celestine (Box 89)
  - Davenport, Daniel (Box 90)
  - Davenport, Marjorie Kendal (Box 90)
    ("Marjorie Merwin")
  - Davenport, Walter (Box 90)
  - Davidson, Lionel (Box 90)
  - Davidson, Robert L. (Box 90)
  - Davidson, Wilson T. (Box 90)
  - Davies, Hunter (Edward H.D.) (Box 90)
  - Davies, Joseph Edward (Box 90)
  - Davies, Lawrence E. (Box 90)
  - Davies, Rhys Vivian (Box 90)
  - Davila, Carlos (Box 91)
  - Davis, A.M. (Box 91)
  - Davis, Alexander G. (Box 91)
  - Davis, Bob (Box 91)
    ("Joe Brandon")
  - Davis, Burton (Box 91)
  - Davis, Douglas M. (Box 91)
  - Davis, Emmett (Box 91)
  - Davis, Fitzroy (Box 91-92)
  - Davis, Forrest (Box 92)
  - Davis, Garry (Box 92)
  - Davis, H.P. (Box 92)
  - Davis, Irving Kaye (Box 92)
  - Davis, John C. (Box 92)
  - Davis, Lou Ellen (Box 92)
    ("Elizabeth Davis")
  - Davis, Margaret (Box 92)
  - Davis, Robert Hobart (Box 92)
  - Davison, Gladys (Box 92)
  - Dawe, Louise Belote (Box 92)
  - Dawson, Leo H. (Box 92)
  - Dayal, Rajeshwar (Box 92)
  - Dealey, Ted (Box 92)
  - Dean, Amber (Amber Dean Getzin) (Box 93)
  - Dean, Jane E. (Box 93)
  - Deane, Shirley (Box 94)
  - Deans, Robert Barr (Box 94)
  - De Blanck, Willy (Box 94)
  - DeBona, Joe (Box 94)
  - Decker, William B. (Box 94)
  - De Combray, Richard (Box 94)
  - De Grandcourt, Charles (Box 94)
  - De Grouchy, William J. (Box 94)
  - De Kay, Ormonde, Jr. (Box 94)
  - Dekobra, Maurice (Box 94)
  - Delaney, Frank (Box 94)
  - Delattre, Pierre Henri (Box 94)
  - De Neufville, Richard (Box 95)
  - Denham, Alice (Box 95)
  - Denham, Bertie (Bertram Stanley Mitford Bowyer, 2nd Baron Denham) (Box 95)
  - Denny, Harold Norman (Box 95)
  - Deptula, Walter J. (Box 96)
  - Derby, August in (Box 96)
  - Detzer, Karl (Box 96)
  - Deuel, William K. (Box 97)
  - Deutsch, Keith (Box 97)
  - Devlin, Patrick Arthur Devlin, Baron (Box 97)
  - Devol, Edmund (Box 97)
  - De Witt, Jack (Box 97)
  - Dickerson, George # (Box 97)
  - Dickson, Gregory (Box 97)
  - Dickson, James Brian (Box 97)
  - Dilke, Annabel (Box 97)
  - Dill, Marshall, Jr. (Box 97)
  - Dillenbeck, A.O. (Box 97)
  - Dimbleby, Josceline Rose Gaskell (Box 97)
  - Diner, Steven (Box 97)
  - Dinneen, Joseph F. (Box 97)
  - Dix, Marion (Box 97)
  - Dixon, George (Box 97)
  - Dixon, Helen (Box 97)
  - Dobie, James Frank (Box 97)
  - Dobson, Rosemary (Box 97)
  - Dodd, Lawrence (Box 97)
  - Dodd, Wayne (Box 97)
  - Dodge, Marion (Marion Dodge Beardsley) (Box 97)
  - Dohrman, Richard (Box 98)
  - Dolgorouky, Princess Stéphanie (Box 99)
  - Dolson, Hildegarde (Hildegarde D. Lockridge, Mrs. Richard Lockridge) (Box 99)
  - Dombrowski zu Papros und Krusvic, Käthe Schonberger von (Box 100)
  - Donovan, Harry (Box 100)
  - Donovan, William V. (Box 100)
  - Dorelis (Box 100)
  - Doremus, Thomas E. (Box 100)
  - Dorien, Ray (Miss E.R. Dingle) (Box 100)
  - Dorrance, Gordon (Box 100)
  - Doubleday, Florence Van Wyck (Mrs. Frank N.) (Box 100)
  - Doubtfire, Dianne Joan (Box 100)
  - Douglas, A.R. (Box 100)
  - Douglas, Albert (Box 100)
  - Doulens, Humphrey (Box 100)
  - Downes, Olin (Box 100)
  - Downey, Fairfax Davis (Box 100)
  - Downey, Harris (Box 100)
  - Downs, William Randall (Box 100)
  - Doyle, Sir Arthur Conan-Estate (Box 101-103)
    (Adrian Malcolm Conan Doyle, etc.)
  - Doyle, Jack (Box 104)
  - Dozer, David (Box 104)
  - Draper, Arthur Stimson (Box 104)
  - Dressier, David (Box 104)
  - Drew, Patricia (Box 104)
  - Drewe, Robert (Box 104)
  - Drewry, John Eldridge (Box 104)
  - Driver, Tom Faw (Box 104)
  - Drucker, Peter Ferdinand (Box 105)
  - Drutman, Irving (Box 105)
  - Dryer, Bernard (Box 105)
  - Dryer, Sherman H. (Box 105)
  - Duggan, Alfred (Box 105)
  - Du Maurier, Daphne (Box 105)
  - Dumesnil, Maurice (Box 105)
  - Dumke, Glenn S. (Box 105)
  - Dumm, Edwina (Box 105)
  - Dunaev, Nicholas A. (Box 106)
  - Dunbar, Janet (Box 106)
  - Dundy, Elaine Brimberg (Box 106)
  - Dunleavy, Yvonne & Elizabeth Ray (Box 106)
  - Dunn, Isabel Burroughs (Box 107)
  - Dunn, Nell (Box 107)
  - Dunn, William J (Box 107)
  - Dunning, Lawrence (Box 107)
  - Dunphy, Jack (Box 107)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, l8th Baron (Box 107)
  - Du Puy, William Atherton (Box 107)
  - Durant, Will (Box 107)
  - Durbridge, Francis Henry (Box 107)
  - Durrell, Gerald Malcolm (Box 108)
  - Durrell, Jacqueline Sonia Rasen (Box 108)
  - Durrell, Lawrence George (Box 108)
  - Eagan, James (Box 109)
  - Early, Stephen (Box 109)
  - Easley, Peter (Ronald M. Easley, Jr.) (Box 109)
  - Easterbrook, James (Box 109)
  - Eastman, Don (Box 109)
  - Eastman, John (Box 109)
  - Easton, Edward (Box 109)
  - Ebel, Suzanne (Box 109)
    ("Suzanne Goodwin" & "Cecily Shelbourne")
  - Eberbach, William K. (Box 109)
  - Eberle, Irmengarde (Box 109)
  - Echard, Margaret (Box 110)
  - Eddison, Eric Rucker (Box 111)
  - Eddy, Clyde L. (Box 111)
  - Edgelow, Thomas (Box 111)
  - Edmonds, Donald C. (Box 111)
  - Edson, Charles L (Box 111)
  - Edwards, Charlotte 8s Tom (Box 111)
  - Edwards, Gilliam (Box 111)
  - Edwards, Monica (Box 111)
  - Edwards, William Waller (Box 111)
  - Egginton, Joyce (Box 111)
  - Ehrenberg, Ilya (Box 111)
  - Ehrgott, Winston W. (Box 111)
  - Ehrlich, Bert (Box 111)
  - Ehrlich, Blake (Box 111)
  - Eichel, Mabel Jacques (Box 111)
  - Eichenhorn, Shelley (Shelley Aspaklaria). (Box 111)
  - El-Ad, Avri (Avri Seidenwerg) & James R, Creech, II (Box 111)
  - Elegant, Robert S. (Box 111)
  - Eliot, Alexander (Box 112)
  - Ellenzweig, Allen (Box 112)
  - Ellerbeck, Rosemary "Nicola Thorne" (Box 112)
  - Ellingston, John R. (Box 113)
  - Elliott, Eleanor Lansing Thomas (Box 113)
  - Elliott, Janice (Janice Cooper) (Box 113)
  - Ellis, Edward Robb (Box 113)
  - Ellis, Fred (Box 113)
  - Ellis, Ralph (Box 113)
  - Elliston, Valerie (Valerie Watkinson) (Box 113)
  - Elsna, Hebe (Box 114)
    ("Laura Conway", "Lyndon Snow", (Dorothy Keogh))
  - Elward, James (Box 114)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers (Box 114)
  - Emecheta, Buchi (Box 114)
  - Emmens, Robert G. (Box 114)
  - Emmet, Christopher T., Jr. (Box 114)
  - Emrich, Duncan (Box 114-115)
  - Engh, Keith & Lenore Glen (Adèle Reed) (Box 115)
  - Engelmann, Peter (Box 115)
  - Engler, Robert (Box 115)
  - Epstein, Helen (Box 115)
  - Erdman, Paul (Box 116)
  - Erdman, Robert Park (Box 116)
  - Erne, Harry (Henry George Victor John Crichton, 6th Earl of Erne) & Raoul Millais (Box 116)
  - Ernst, Morris Leopold (Box 116)
  - Erskine, John (Box 116)
  - Erskine-Lindop, Audrey Beatrice Noël (Box 116)
  - Eskew, Garnett L. (Box 116)
  - Espy, Reeves (Box 116)
  - Esslin, Martin Julius (Box 116)
  - Estabrooks, George Hoben (Box 116)
  - Estey, Norbert (Box 116)
  - Estridge, Robin (Box 116)
    ("Philip Loraine", "Robert York")
  - Eulich, Margaret Sally (Box 117)
  - Eustis, Helen (Box 117)
  - Evans, Colin (Box 117)
  - Evans, David A, "Lewis Arnold" (Box 117)
  - Evans, Douglas & Charles Cospatrick Douglas-Home (Box 117)
  - Evans, Elizabeth (Box 117)
  - Evans, Frank E« (Box 117)
  - Eysenck, Hans Jurgen (Box 117)
  - Faber, Nancy (Box 118)
  - Fahnestock, Mary Sheridan (Mrs. Bruce) (Box 118)
  - Fain, William (Box 118)
  - Fairservis, Walter A., Jr. (Box 118)
  - Falls, Cyril Bentham (Box 118)
  - Farmer, Etta (Box 118)
  - Farnsworth, Sam (Box 118)
  - Farr, Robert (Box 118)
  - Farrell, Edward F (Box 118)
  - Faulk, Terry R. (Box 118)
  - Fawcett, James Waldo (Box 118)
  - Fay, Judith (Box 118)
  - Feagles, Anita McRae (Box 119)
  - Feeley, Constance (Constance F. Reed) (Box 119)
  - Feland, Logan (Box 119)
  - Felger, Richard (Box 119)
  - Fenby, Jonathan (Box 119)
  - Ferber, Ellen (Box 119)
  - Fergusson, Adam Dugdale (Box 120)
  - Ferrier, Ben & Marion Z. (Box 120)
  - Ferris, Paul Frederick (Box 120)
  - Ferris, Walter (Box 120)
  - Ferro, Robert (Box 120)
    ("Alec Sassoon")
  - Field, Andrew (Box 121)
  - Field, Dawn Stewart (Box 121)
  - Field, John (Box 121)
  - Fielding, Daphne Winifred Louise Vivian Thynne (Box 121)
  - Filene, Edward Albert (Box 121)
  - Finch, Percy & Barbara Miller Finch (Box 121)
  - Fine, John C. (Box 121)
  - Fine, Peter Heath (Box 121)
  - Finkel, George (Box 121)
  - Fischer, Steven Roger (Box 121)
  - Fishback, David D. (Box 121)
  - Fisher, Boyd (Box 121)
  - Fisz, Ginette (Ginette Chevallier) (Box 121)
  - Fitch, Clyde (Box 121)
  - Fitz, Jean DeWitt (Box 121)
  - FitzGerald, John J. & J.V. (Box 121)
  - Fitzsimmons, Mrs. Robert Prometheus (Box 121)
  - Fitzsimons, Christopher (Box 121)
  - Fleetwood, Hugh N. (Box 122)
  - Fletcher, Chrys Paul (Robert Edward Mills) (Box 122)
  - Fletcher, David (Box 122)
  - Fletcher, Frank Irving (Box 122)
  - Fletcher, Grace Nies (Box 122)
  - Fletcher, Ronald (Box 122)
  - Fliegers, Serge (Box 122)
  - Flower, Sibylla Jane (Box 122)
  - Flowers, Charles Howard (Box 122)
  - Floyd, Bryan Alec (Box 122)
  - Fludas, John (Box 122)
  - Flynn, Edward Joseph (Box 122)
  - Foldes, Andor & Lili Rendy-Foldes (Box 122)
  - Foley, Martha (Box 122)
  - Folster, George Thomas (Box 122)
  - Foote, Timothy (Box 122)
  - Forbes, Edna Kent (Box 122)
  - Ford, Daniel (Box 122)
  - Ford, Ford Madox (Box 122)
  - Ford, James Allan (Box 122)
  - Forma, Warren (Box 122)
  - Forman, Harrison (Box 122)
  - Forssmann, Werner (Box 123)
  - Forster, Margaret (Box 123)
  - Forster, Peter (Box 123)
  - Forsyth, Frederick M (Box 123)
  - Foster, Florence (Box 123)
  - Fowler, Peter Jon (Box 123)
  - Fox, Edward Seccomb (Box 123)
  - Fox, Fontaine Talbot, Jr. (Box 123)
  - Foxell, Nigel (Box 123)
  - Foyle, Kathleen (Box 123)
  - Franck, Harry Alverson (Box 124)
  - Frank, Rosalie H (Box 124)
  - Frankau, Pamela (Box 124)
  - Frankel, Paul H. (Box 124)
  - Franklin, Sidney (Box 124)
  - Fraser, Lady Antonia Pakenham (Box 124)
  - Fraser, Bryce (Box 124)
  - Fraser, Ferrin L. & Beatrice Ryan Fraser (Box 125)
  - Fraser, Hugh Charles Patrick Joseph & Diana Barnato Walker (Box 125)
  - Fraser, Sylvia (Box 125)
  - Fraser, W. Lionel (Box 125)
  - Frazer, Charles C. (Box 125)
  - Free, Marion Allen (Box 126)
  - Freedman, Benedict (Box 126)
  - Freedman, David (Box 126)
  - Freeling, Nicolas (Box 126)
  - Freeman, Everett (Box 126)
  - Freeman, Gillian (Box 126)
  - Freeman, Joseph (Box 126)
  - French, Fergus (Peter Friedlaender) (Box 126)
  - French, Jere Stuart (Box 126)
  - Fried, Barbara (Box 126)
  - Friede, Donald (Box 126)
  - Friedman, Esther & Aaron (Esther Lear) (Box 126)
  - Friedman, Roy (Box 126)
  - Friend, Donald (Box 126)
  - Friendly, Alfred (Box 126)
  - Frisby, John (Box 126)
  - Frisch, Paul Z. & Ann (Box 126)
  - Frost, David (Box 126-127)
  - Frostick, Michael (Box 127)
  - Fructoso, Mario (Box 127)
  - Fruetel, Hal (Box 127)
  - Fulcher, Gordon B. (Box 127)
  - Fuller, Roy Broadbent (Box 127)
  - Fullerton, Hugh (Box 127)
  - Fullmer, Richard (Box 127)
    ("Dirk Vanden")
  - Funk, Peter V.K. (Box 127)
  - Furbank, P.N. & Mary Lago (Box 127)
  - Furcolowe, Charles (Box 127)
  - Futter, Walter (Box 127)
  - Fyson, Mama Elizabeth (Box 127)
  - Fytton, Francis (Charles Farid Bassili Francis Fytton) (Box 127)
  - Gabriel, Gilbert Wolf (Box 128)
  - Gabrysh, Andrew F. (Box 128)
  - Gade, John Allyne • (Box 128)